reedeu.com 2009-01-31

# Reed Exhibition // Exhibitor University

| 

Privacy Policy

The effective date of this policy as posted is March 23, 2004.

Reed Exhibitions and Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University respect the information provided by our customers. Because we gather certain types of information when our customers communicate with us, we believe you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the information we capture and the use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the type of information we capture about our customers, how we use it to communicate with our customers, and how you can request to no longer receive communications from Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University. 

US Policy

Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University is produced and managed by Reed Exhibitions United States (Reed-US), a division of Reed Elsevier, Inc. This privacy policy applies to all Reed-US offices and conforms to the spirit of the Reed Exhibitions Corporate Privacy Policy, which can be found at [www.reedexpo.com](http://www.reedexpo.com/). 

Our Customers

This policy applies to all customers of Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University and Reed-US, who include but are not limited to, our show exhibitors, show visitors, conference visitors, customer inquiries, speakers, press, and other individuals with whom Reed-US maintains business relationships or communications. 

Customer Information and Use

Two primary types of information are gathered about our customers:

Financial Information is payment information used for or gathered during the registration process and includes, but is not limited to, credit card numbers, financial institutions, and expiration dates. This information is not used for any purpose other than that for which it is being provided to us, and is used only to the extent necessary for processing the transaction or to facilitate future transactions.

Professional Information includes, but is not limited to, name, address, company name, company address, phone number, fax number, and email address, as well as questions answered on survey or registration forms. Data captured during a customer’s visit to the Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University web site, as well as during a visit with a Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University customer is also considered professional information and may also be stored in our customer database for our internal use. Professional information may be, upon the consent of Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University, shared with other organizations or Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University customers for the purpose of facilitating business relationships believed by Reed-US to be in our customers’ best interests.

Opting Out

Reed-US will accept, implement and maintain any customer request to opt out of future communication from Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University, Reed-US, or a third party to whom Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University provided the customer’s information. If you would like to opt out of communications you are receiving from Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University, Reed-US, or a third party contacting you on behalf of Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University, please click here and enter the information requested so we may thoroughly implement your request within 10 days of receipt.

Security

This site utilizes a secure server to protect your financial and professional information. Secure server software is used to encrypt the information sent between your Internet browser and our Internet site. This ensures the security of your professional and financial transaction details when using the site. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information you have given to us and may, on occasion, request proof of identity before we disclose any professional information to you.  

Method of Transaction Security

Products of Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to safeguard customer information during online transactions. SSL encryption is the generally accepted method of transaction security in online ordering.

Cookies

A "cookie" is a bit of data sent by a website through the browser to the computer of the user visiting the site, and enables the site to return the results the browser expects. The Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University website uses temporary, session-specific cookies to ensure visits to its websites are smooth and customized for the visitor. Such cookies allow us to provide a visitor's browser with information tailored to the visitor's preferences and needs. We use permanent or persistent cookies that remain on a visitor's computer after the visitor leaves the Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University website. However, our cookies neither reveal nor contain any identifying or personal data. Cookies also cannot read any information on a visitor's computer or interact with other cookies on the visitor's hard drive.

If you do not want your browser to accept cookies, you can turn off the cookie acceptance option in the browser's settings. However, disabling the cookie support function of the browser will prevent our website from functioning properly and you may not be able to utilize fully all of the site's features and information.

Policy Changes

Reed-US reserves the right to review and change this Policy. Policy changes may be made without prior notice to existing customers. Policy revisions only apply to information gathered as of the effective date of the revised policy, unless we give you notice and choice as to the changes in use, in which case all information is subject to the new policy.

Review and Correction of Customer Information or Other Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about your customer information or your request to opt-out of communications from Reed Exhibitions Exhibitor University or its third party partners, or if you would like to review the information we’ve collected about you, please call or write our Privacy Administrator:

> Reed Exhibitions  
>  US Privacy Administrator/Database Dept  
>  383 Main Ave.  
>  Norwalk, CT 06851
> 
> Phone: Within the US at 888-306-2344   
>  Outside the US at 203-840-5810   
>  Email: [privacy@reedexpo.com](mailto:privacy@reedexpo.com)

|
